John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Works By Tukey, 1938-1994; 25 linear feet
  - Subseries A. Papers, 14 linear feet
    - Supplement to Technical Report 269, Series 2, 1984 July 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Survey of Sampling from Contaminated Distributions, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Symposium on Sampling Bulk Materials, 1951 June 18; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Systemization of Journal Practices, 1955; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Tagging Scheme for "Journals", n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Tagging System for Journal Articles and Other Citable Items: A Status Report, A, 1963; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Teaching of Concrete Mathematics, 1958; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Technical Tools of Statistics, 1965; 10 items; Tukey, John W
    - Techniques for the Graphical Analysis of Possibly Skewed Measurements, 1989; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L, Joseph F. Heyse and John W. Tukey
    - Telephone Dialling Techniques Based on Move-THEN-Take Control, 1975 February 26; 1 item; Mathews, M. V. and John W. Tukey
    - Teletypewriter Plots for Data Analysis can be Fast: 6-line Plots, Including Probability Plots, 1973; 1 item; Andrews, David F. and John W. Tukey
    - Testing for the Inclusion of Variables in Linear Regression by a Randomization Technique: Comments and Corrections, 3 items; Hoaglin, David. C. and John W. Tukey
    - Testing Peripheral Association, 1947; 1 item; Olmstead, P. S. and John W. Tukey
    - Testing the Statistical Certainty of a Response to Increasing Doses of a Drug, 1985; 1 item; Ciminera, J. L., J. F. Heyse, and John W. Tukey
    - Testing Unit Vectors for Correlation, 1971; Epp, R. J., John W. Tukey, and G. S. Watson
    - Tests for Non-Additivity, 1970; 3 items; Federer, W. T., D. S. Robson and John W. Tukey
    - Tests for Qualitative Treatment-by-Centre Interaction Using a 'Pushback' Procedure, 1990; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L., Joseph F. Heyse, Nguyen, Ha H., and John W. Tukey
    - Theorum-using, Asymptomatic Approximate, and Empirical Mathematics; Which A as a Foundation for Data Analysis, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Theory of Intersteller Polarization, A, 1951; 1 item; Spitzer, Lyman, Jr., and John W. Tukey
    - Theory of Statistical Estimation, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Things We Need To Do For Small n, 1981 October 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Think Piece #3 on the Canyon Problem: One Random Sample and Some Graphics, 1988 May 2; 2 item; Tukey, John W
    - Thinking About Non-Linear Smoothers, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Those Erroneous Plots, n.d.; 1 items; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on Pearson Curves, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on Polynomial Regression: --the Stopping Problem-- Stimulated by Discussion with Stoller, 1957; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on Statistical Analysis of Multi-dose Experiments, 1984; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on Subdivision, 1992; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on the Analysis of Leveled Gaps, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on the Evolution of Dynamic Graphics for Data-Modification Display, 1983; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Thoughts on the Practical Assessment of Variability of Estimates of Variance, and its Use in Selecting Widthers, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Three Suggestions for Don McNeil's Regression Programming, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Three- and More-Way Analysis: The Main-Effects-Only Case, 1979 September 26; 1 item; Romanowicz, Nancy and John W. Tukey
    - Three-Word Access with Brarnching Lengths, 1987 October 30; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Three-Year Forecast of Educational Computer Needs, A, n.d.; 1 item; Committee on Uses of Computers
    - Thresholds of Attention in Exploratory Data Analysis, 1987 September 14; 3 items; Marsh, Catharine and John W. Tukey
    - Tightening of Clinical Trials, 1993; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Time Series Alanysis (Not Analysis), 1962; 3 items; Bogert, Bruce P., M. J. R. Healy and John W. Tukey
    - Time Series, n.d.; 5 items; Tukey, John W
    - Timing of the Distribution of Events Between Observations: A Contribution to the Study of Follow-up Studies, 1950; 12 items; Harris, T. E., Paul Meier, and John W. Tukey
    - Timing of the Distribution of Events Between Observations, 1950; 1 item; Harris, T. E., Paul Meier, and John W. Tukey
    - Tools for Large Two-Way Tables: Multipolishing, 1995; 2 item; Morganthaler, Stephen and John W. Tukey
    - Towards Robust Analysis of Variance I, 1998; 4 items; Seheult, Allan and John W. Tukey
    - Tracking Studies - Analysis of Servo Performance by Regression, 1949 January 20; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Transfactorial Fits 1. The Linear Geometry in the Two-Way Case, 1977; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Transformation of Beta Distribution, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Transformation Related to the Angular and the Square Root, 1950; 2 item; Freeeman, Murray F. and John W. Tukey
    - Truncated Mean in Moderately Large Samples, The, 1949 July 18; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Tuberculin Tests of the Mercy Hospital Nurses, 1947 November 26; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Tumorigenicity Assays, Including Use of the Jackknife, n.d.; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L., Joseph F. Heyse, Nathan Mantel and John W. Tukey
    - Tuning a Major Part of a Clustering Algorithm, 1991; 1 item; Hansen, Katherine M. and John W. Tukey
    - Two-Way Plots of Multipolished Tables, 1998; 1 item; Morganthaler, Stephan, and John W. Tukey
    - Two-Way Plots: I. The Case of Linear Traces, 1999; 1 item; Morganthaler, Stephan, and John W. Tukey
    - Understanding Robust and Exploratory Data Analysis, 1981; 1 item; Hoaglin, David C., Frederick Mosteller, and John W. Tukey
    - Understanding Some Long-Tailed Symmetrical Distributions, 1972; 1 item; Rogers, William H. and John W. Tukey
    - Unsolved Problems of Experimental Statistics, 1953; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Urban Trends in Male and Female Lung Cancer Mortality in the U.S. Counties 1970-1987, 1992; 1 item; Freedman, Laurence S., Colin Goodall, Karen Kafadar, and John W. Tukey
    - Usable Resistant/Robust Techniques of Analysis, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Augmented Box Plots for Reviewing Mearsurement Results Collected Over Time, 1988; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L. and John W. Tukey
    - Use of Control Clissifications: Adjustment for Inadequacy of Broad Classes (Souvenir Sheet), 1962; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Double Sampling in Studying Robustness, The, 1984; 1 item; Morganthaler, Stephan, and John W. Tukey
    - Use of Equalization (Approximate Inverse Transfer Functions) to Determine the Initial Sense of Earthquake waves, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Funom in Trajectory Fitting Problems, 1960 May; 1 item; Tukey,John W
    - Use of Many Covariates in Clinical Trials, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Multiple Arrays in Seismic Detection, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Notched Box Plots for 'Normal' Laboratory Values II. More Careful Study of Large Groups of Data, n.d.; 2 items; Ciminera, Joseph L. and John W. Tukey
    - Use of Notched Box Plots for (Physiologically) 'Normal' Laboratory Values I. Routine Procedure, n.d.; I item; Ciminera, Joseph L. and John W. Tukey
    - Use of Numerical Spectrum Analysis in Geophysics, n.d.; 1 items; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Reference Standards, The, 1951; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Use of Smelting in Guiding Re-Expression, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Uses and Usefulness of Binomial Probability Paper, The, 1949; 1 item; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Uses of Numerical Spectrum Analysis in Geophysics, 1965; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Using Probability Calculations for Greater Safety, Not Less, 1986; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Using the H-Matrix to Find Out Groups, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Validating Detectable Differences, 1988 August 4; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variance Components for Regression Situations, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Variance of Means of Symmetrically Trimmed Samples From Normal Populations, and its Estimation From Such Trimmed Samples, The, 1961; 1 item; McLaughlin, Donald H. and John W. Tukey
    - Variance of Slopes of Lines Fitted to Groups: An Analysis of the Johnstone and Velleman Monte Carlo Results, The, 1984; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variance, and Mean, of Transformed Variates and the Standardized Distances Between Symetrical % Points of Pearson Curves, The, 1 item; Pearson, E. S., John W. Tukey and C. P. Winsor
    - Variances for Sample Size 20, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variances of Variance Components: I. Balanced Designs, 1956; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variances of Variance Components: II. The Unbalanced Single Classification, 1957; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variances of Variance Components: III. Third Moments in a Balanced Single Classification, 1957; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variations of Box Plots, n.d.; 1 item; Larsen, Wayne A., Robert McGill, and John W. Tukey
    - Varied Faces of Pollution, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Variety of Useful Representations for 2nd Degree Order Statistic Moments Illustrated, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Various Methods from a Unified Point of View (Reminder Sheet), 1952; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Vector Methods in the Analysis of Variance, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Visual Display in the Decades to Come, 1988; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - W. Edwards Deming Medal Acceptance Speech, 1983 December 1; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Wandering Schematic Plot, 1980; 2 items; Parunak, Anita and John W. Tukey
    - Warning About Statistical Efficiency, A, 1945; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Was Isaac Newton a Credulous Alchemist, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Way Forward for Robust Regression, A, 1973; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - We Need Both Exploratory and Confirmatory, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Weighting in Configural Polysampling, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What Can Data Analysis and Statistics Offer Today?, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What Can Mathematicians Do for the Federal Government?, 1967; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What do Covariates do to Cox Proportional-Hazards Regression, 1990; items; Halpern, Jerry, and John W. Tukey
    - What Does the Mean-Square-Successive-Difference Measure When Applied to Time Series?, 1950 September 28; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What Have Statisticians Been Forgetting?, 1967; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What is an Analysis of Variance? By T.P. Speed. Discussion., 1986; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - What is an Auxillary Function?n.d., 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What is Exploratory Data Analysis and a Little About How, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What is Statistics?, 1965 September 26; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What is Topology?, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What Kind of a Confidence Interval? That kind of a Confidence Interval!!!, 1991 May 14; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - What Modern Statistical Techniques Might do for Forecasting, 1977; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What Should Fitted Polynomials be Taken as Estimating, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - What--and Whay--is a Main Effect, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - When Should Which Spectrum Approach be Used?, n.d.; 7 items; Tukey, John W
    - Where Do We Go From Here?, 1960; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Where Should Multiple Comparisons Go Next, 1991; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Which Part of the Sample Contains the Information, Tukey, John W
    - Why the Bereg Calsulation Might Have a Larger Variance, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Words Following Many Other Words, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Work on General Tools, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Worked Example and Some Further Lessons, A, 1981 March 11; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - XXNN, an Unexploited Opportunity, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - You and Mathematics, Comments, 1963; 34 items
    - You and Mathematics, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Yule's Association Paradox and Ignored Stratum Heterogeneity in Capture-Recapture Studies, 2 items; Kadane, Joseph B., Michael M. Meyer, and John W. Tukey
    - Zeroth Draft of Specifications for Empirically-guided-classification Support System, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Zig-zagging Climb from Initial Observation to Successful Improvement, The, 1973; 1 item; Tukey, John W
  - Subseries B. Talks, 1 linear foot
    Tukey was not only a highly productive writer but was also an active speaker. Included within the Talks sub-series are interviews, conference lectures and paper presentations, and panel discussions. Some of Tukey’s lectures, such as Statistician's and Today's Conflicts, were later published as papers and can be found in Tukey’s Collected Works. On a few occasions Tukey was asked to testify before the U.S. House of representatives and the U.S. Senate regarding issues such as the census and the environment. Transcripts of his testimony including his statement as a Member of U.S. Delegation to Technical Working Group Two, Geneva Test Ban Conference are included in this sub-series. Of special note is an interview with Tukey and Albert Tucker which details Tukey’s thoughts on the Princeton mathematics community in the 1930s.
    - Analysis of Data: Connectiong the Future with the Past, The, 1976; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Data: Exploration as One Road to Discovery, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Bureau of the Census: Second Annual Research Conference, March 23-26, 1986, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments Made Before, Between, and After the Papers of the third Session of the Computer Symposium, 21 June 1966, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Configural and Polysampling Methods in the Study of Robustness, 1982; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Contributions to Discussion, 1970; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Current Ideas and Approaches to making Information Useful, Illustrated by a Hypothetical Laboratories' Memorandum System, 1962; 18 items; Tukey, John W
    - Detection, Inspection, and the Nuclear Test Ban Agreement, 1960; 1 item; Goldman, Eric F., Jay Orear, John W. Tukey, and Hugh C. Wolfe
    - Direct Testimony of Dr. John W. Tukey Sampling Methods and Procedures, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion (of Papers on Outliers), n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion 2 - Mixture Modeling vs. Selection Modeling with Non-Ignorable Non-Response - Donald Rubin and Robert Glynn, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion 3: Alternative Methods for Evaluating the Impact of Intervention, 1986; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion 4: Mixture Modeling Versus Selection Modeling with Monignorable Nonresponse, 1986; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion Given at 1968 Proceedings of the American Statistical Association Social Statistics Section, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion of Paper by Herbert Schimmel, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion of Paper by Lave and Seskin, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion of the Papers of Messrs. Anscombe and Daniel, 1960; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion: Royal Statistical Society (Series A, 148), 1985; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion: What Can Data Analysis and Statistics Offer Today?, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Discussion: What is an Analysis by T. P. Speed, Tukey, John W
    - Discussion: What is Projection Pursuit by M.C. Jones and R. Sibson, 1987; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Econometrics, 1969 October 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Exploratory Data Analysis as Part of a Larger Whole, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Exploratory Data Anlysis, 1995-2000, 1993; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Frederick Mosteller and John W. Tukey: A Conversation, 1988; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Future of Departments of Statistics, The, 1968; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Guided Re-expression at the ASA Short Course, San Diego, 1978, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Inevitable Collision Between Computation and Data Analysis, The, 1963; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Interview with John Tukey at Princeton University (with Albert Tucker), 1984; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Introduction to Guided Re-expression, 1977; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Kendall Sum, The, 1950; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Measuring Educational Progress: A Study of the National Assessment of Educational Progress, 1975; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Methods for Direct and Indirect Graphic Display for Data Sets in 3 and More Dimensions, I-III, 1980; 3 items; Tukey, John W and Paul Tukey
    - More Honest Foundations for Data Analysis, 1994; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Murray Hill Statistics Seminar, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Panel Discussion on How and Where do Statisticians Fit in, 1956; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Practical Robustness in Contect, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Princeton Analysis of the 20-year Cancer Deaths by County: General Philosophy, The, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Proceedings of the 1977 Doe Statistical Symposium: Panel Discussion, 2 items; Bennet, Carl A., Fred Leone, Herbert J. C. Kouts, Richard L. Hooper, and John W. Tukey
    - Proposed Testimony of John W. Tukey before the Subcommittee on the Environment and the Atmosphere of the Committee on Science and Technology U.S. House of Representatives, 1975; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Recipient of the W. Edwards Deming Medal American Society for Quality Control, Metropolitan Section, 1983 December 1; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Regarding Priestley's Processes with Slowly Changing Spectra, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Remarks by JWT at AMS Conference, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Remarks of John W. Tukey Upon Presentation of the James Madison Medal at Princeton University, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Remarks on the Gilliland Report, 1963; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Research Needs on Environmental Health, 1966; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Response on Accepting the 1990 Award for Distinquished Service to Measurement at the Invitational Conference, Educational Testing Service, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Role of Statistics, The, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Rough Draft of Discussion for Detroit, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Royal Statistical Society Paper, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Scott Lecture, 1st, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Scott Lecture, 2nd, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Seminar on Statistics of Noise, Lecture 1, 1952; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Shewhart-ASQC Talk, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Sigma Xi Talk, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Social Programs Evaluation Conference, 1974; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Some Perspectives on Data Analysis, 1967; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Spectrum of a Time Function (IEEE Proceedings), 1981; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Spes in the Years Ahead, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Standard Methods of Analyzing Data, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Statement of Dr. John W. Tukey, Member of U.S. Delegation to Technical Working Group Two, Geneva Test Ban Conference, 1960; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Statement of John Tukey, Chairman National Reasearch Council Climate Impact Committee before the Subcommittee on the Upper Atmosphere of the Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences U.S. Senate, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Statistical Response, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Statisticians and Today's Conflicts, 1984; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Statistics for the Operations Analyst, 1962; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Strategy and tactics of Developing Data Analysis Techniques, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Talk at Raleigh, 1960; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Technical Tools of Statistics, The, 1964; 9 items; Tukey, John W
    - Testimony of John W. Tukey before the Subcommittee on Census and Population Committee on Post Office and Civil Service United States House of Representatives, 1990; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Transcript of Discussion with John Tukey, Eugene Johnson, Jim Carlson, John Mazzeo, 1994; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Wald Lectures, 1958; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - We Need Both Exploratory and Confirmatory, 1980; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Where Should we be Going, 1996; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Workshop on Future Directions in Signal Processing, 1973; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - XXNN, an Unexploited Opportunity, 1985; 1 item; Tukey, John W
- Series III. Works By Others, 1937-2000; 3 linear feet
  The Works by Others Series is three linear feet arranged alphabetically by Author’s last name. Order was imposed as the material arrived disorganized and Tukey’s intended method for keeping the materials wasn’t apparent. Within this series are papers by colleagues and collaborators, some former students. The material within this series reflects Tukey’s role as constructive critic and contributor to those who sought his opinion on statistical and mathematical matters.
  The retention criteria for material within this series is limited to work with which Tukey directly contributed or influenced. We retained some material, however, because it is commentary on work by Tukey himself. The following are examples of material that falls into this category: by E. Kaplan, Comments on Tukey’s Multiple Comparisons; by Harold W. Kuhn, Notes of a Problem by Tukey; by Howard Wainer, Graphical Visions from William Playfair to John Tukey.
  - Serial Statistics: Is Radioactive Decay Random?, 1973; 14 items; Anderson, John Lynde and George Wesley Spangler (Box 1)
  - Some Scaling Models and Estimation Procedures in the Latent Class Model, 1 item; Anderson, T.W (Box 1)
  - Finding the Outliers that Matter, 1977 March; 1 item; Andrews, David F. and Daryl Pregibon (Box 1)
  - Some Monte Carlo Results on Robust/Resistant Regression, 1973; 12 items; Andrews, David F (Box 1)
  - Looking at Two-way Tables, 1982; 3 items; Anscombe, Francis John (Box 1)
  - Transformation of Poisson, Binomial and Negative-Binomial Data, 1 item; Anscombe, Francis John (Box 1)
  - Approximate Tests and Confidence Intervals Using the Jackknife, 1971; 5 items; Arvesen, James N. and David S. Salsburg (Box 1)
  - Detection and Monitoring of CO2-Induced Climate Changes, 1983; 3 items; Baker, D. James, W. Lawrence Gates, Thomas H. Vonder Haar, Michael C. MacCracken, Syukuro Manabe, and Gunter Weller (Box 1)
  - Mixture Clutstering of Univariate Data with Single Member Groups, 1990; 15 items; Basford, Kaye and D. R. Greenway (Box 1)
  - Statistical Estimation Procedure for Probabilistic Functions of Finite Markov Processes, 1967; 2 items; Baum, Leonard E. and Lloyd R. Welch (Box 1)
  - Discussion of "Graphic Comparisons of Several Linked Aspects" by John W. Tukey, 1992; 1 item; Becker, Richard A. and William S. Cleveland (Box 1)
  - Some Computational Details of Configural Sampling, 1981; 1 item; Bell, Katherine, and Daryl Pregibon (Box 1)
  - Proposed Analysis of the Western Electric Environmental Information Survey, A, n.d.; 1 item; Binkowski, E. S (Box 1)
  - Some Blotto Games, 1949-1950; 13 items; Blackett, D. W (Box 1)
  - On the Number of Significant Findings to be Expected by Chance, 1960; 4 items; Block, Jack, 1924-2010 (Box 1)
  - Natural Variability of Vital Rates and Associated Statistics, The, 1986; 2 items; Brillinger, David R. (Box 1)
  - Some History of the Data Analysis of Time Series in the United States, 1974; 3 items; Brillinger, David R. (Box 1)
  - Non-Stationary Velocity Smoothing, 1957; 4 items; Burford, Tom M (Box 1)
  - Pollution - Tukey, n.d.; 2 items; Cahn, Robert (Box 1)
  - Genetic Effects of Irradiation with Reference to Man, 1947; 2 items; Catcheside, D. G (Box 1)
  - Two-Step Acquisition: Modification of an Internal Clock's Criterion, 1984; 6 items; Church, Russell M., Warren H. Meck, and Fariba N. Komeily-Zadeh (Box 1)
  - Mutagenicity of Diesel Exhaust Particle Extracts, 1982; 4 items; Clark, Charles R (Box 1)
  - Grammatical Structure of Tables, n.d.; 2 items; Clark, Nancy (Box 1)